Johann D Aguirre Curry

Phone number: 07555799518 Email: johannaguirre55@gmail.com Nationality: Dual, British/Colombian

Date of Birth: 09/11/1999

100 watch elm close, Bradley stoke BS32 8AN

PERSONAL STATEMENT

With a strong background in leadership and teamwork through working as an outdoor instructor for a year, I am keen to begin an apprenticeship that allows me to both apply and improve my skills while studying for qualifications. I am fluent in both English and Spanish and have extremely good verbal communication as I have experienced different cultures and adapting to new situations with new people is second nature to me. I see the importance of understanding between people and enjoy working with others to generate ideas and work successfully towards a goal. I have a very positive outlook and work to the best of my ability, always going the extra mile in order to succeed regardless of the difficulty of a task.

SKILLS

- Fast and effective learner; I became fluent in English after a year, and achieved my GCSEs in less than 2 years of living in England with no prior experience of the language
- Excellent leadership with the ability to guide and work with groups of all types of people
- Working well in a high-pressure environment and consistently making informed and successful decisions to fit the requirements of a task
- Organisational and planning skills with experience in planning activities, routes and trips and running sessions in outdoor sports
- Quick-thinking and able to generate and act upon appropriate responses to unplanned scenarios

WORK EXPERIENCE

Hope and Anchor Inn 2017-present, The Mousetrap Inn 2015-2017 Part time jobs as front of house and kitchen porter

- Working under pressure during the busy summer season
- Prioritising tasks and ensuring customers are satisfied
- Appropriately dealing with complaints and finding a solution

Dynamic Adventures, Dartington September 2017-September 2018

- Gaining outdoor instructor/coaching qualifications and thereby gaining leadership experience
- Working with and leading a variety of people from all ages, backgrounds and needs and improving my teamworking skills
- Guiding and leading groups of people aboard and taking on large responsibilities such as the safety of the group
- Correctly treating injuries and ensuring customers remain calm in an emergency

'The Really Good Media Company' July 2016 (1 week)

- Gaining understanding of how a small company is run
- Learning how to shoot and edit short films

EDUCATION AND QUALIFICATIONS

The Cotswold School- Bourton On the Water March 2015-July 2017 GCSES

Spanish A*

English language level 4 (predicted for 2019)

English literature level 4

Math's level 5

Core science B

Applied science B

French C

PE C

ART C

Geography D

Dynamic Adventures, Dartington September 2017-September 2018 Outdoor Instructor awards

Paddle sport instructor
MIAS Level 1 (mountain bike leader)
CWI (climbing wall instructor)
Beach life guard
Surf coach
First Aid Level 3
Duke of Edinburgh assessor
Safe guarding course

HOBBIES AND INTERESTS

- Outdoor sports; surfing, white water kayaking
- Keeping fit, going to the gym and playing badminton
- Travelling; I spent 6 weeks on a solo surf trip to Panama and have travelled extensively to Europe, the USA and South America
- Practicing street magic and writing songs

References available on request.

REFERENCES

Outdoor instructor- DYNAMIC ADVENTURES PAUL MICHAEL PHONE 07770815665 Email info@dynamicadventurescic.co.uk

FRONT OF HOUSE-THE MOUSE TRAP AMY STUREG Email <u>amysturge@ymail.com</u>